(561) 699-2743 roody.jerry@yahoo.com linkedin.com/in/roody-pointjour/ github.com/rpointjour/career portfolio

Determined and goal-oriented individual with passion, technical proficiency, and successful track record of completing development projects. Expert in Front-End development to create responsive and dynamic applications with impressive user interface designs. Vast knowledge of Software Development to design, develop, deploy, test, and enhance next generation software technologies.

### **Skills**

	*****
•	HTTN/II
•	

CSS

JavaScript

• Java

- React
- Amazon Web Services
- C
- C++

- Python
- SQL
- MySQL
- Django

# **Experience**

Concierge Technical Support Specialist

### **Colliers International**

Tracked and logged all requests for desktop service in Service-Now

- Imaged laptops, desktops, and workstations
- Provided desk side support for hands-on issues

Business Mobility Technical Support

## **ACG**

Boynton Beach, FL March 2022 – May 2022

Boca Raton, FL

June 2022 - Present

- Troubleshooted advanced technical issues for over 200 business clients
- Solved problems and developed practical solutions for business needs

Front End Developer – WordPress Intern

## **TheaterEars**

Boca Raton, FL

September 2021 – December 2021

- Developed code and troubleshooting for WordPress core
- Created and customized plugins and themes
- CMS/Database Management
- Website Page Construction

# **Projects**

## **Engineering Design**

Summer 2022

TurtleBot 3 Waffle Pi

- Worked with my team to design a robot capable of autonomously following a leader
- Project revolved around the robot following the leader, either human or another robot
- Tracking system involved the use of a lidar sensor and camera to avoid object collisions

### **Intro to Embedded Systems**

Summer 2021

MSP430-G2553

- Utilized programming skills by programming to the MSP430 microcontroller
- Built a project that detects the distance of an object and motion of a person
- Developed a better understanding of programmable hardware

#### **Relevant Coursework**

• Computer Science

Python

Intro to C

• Mobile Apps

Digital Systems

Data Structures

## **Education**

# Florida Atlantic University